Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5552
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- RLEA. Xerox Machine Model 914, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- RLEA. Lawyer - General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Lawyer's Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 18a)
- RLEA. Lawyer's Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 18b)
- RLEA. Strikes, General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway, Strike, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- RLEA. Photos and Articles Re: Safety Hearing, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  Contains several newspaper clippings and 3 black and white photos. Sent in response to a request from the Executive-Secretary.
- RLEA. Financial General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- RLEA. United Farm Workers Strike, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- RLEA. Contracting Out - Sunny Point, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- RLEA. Contracting Out Sunny Point 1967 and 1968, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- RLEA. Air Pollution (New Jersey), 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  Proposed statutes in New Jersey.
- Railroads. Railroads - General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  Contains pamphlet "The American Railroads - An Industry with a Challenge."
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads [folder 1 of 2], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 28a)
  Contains bulletins and statistics.
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads [folder 2 of 2], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 28b)
- Railroads. Penn Central, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Railroads. Association of Western Railways, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Railroads. National Railway Labor Conference, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations, General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Railroads. Southern Pacific Hospital Department, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations, Medicare, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Railroads. Air Freight, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO - General [folder 1 of 2], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 36a)
  Contains newspaper clippings, including an article about American socialism, bulletins, a copy of resolution on Civil Rights, and 1969 Statements.
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO - General [folder 2 of 2], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 36b)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Legislative Council, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Executive Council, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  Pamphlet on disaffiliation of the UAW
- Other Organizations. Miscellaneous Organizational - General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  Thank you notes from the Congressional Secretaries' Club and Ad Book for Celebration of Senator Edmund Muskie.
- Other Organizations. U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Genl. UN), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Other Organizations. Transportation Research Forum, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Other Organizations. Charities - General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Other Organizations. Labor Bureau of Middle West, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Other Organizations. Labor Newspaper, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  By-Laws and financial reports.
- Other Organizations. "Golden Spike", 1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Other Organizations. National Association of Railroad Passengers, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Other Organizations. Conference of Transportation Trades, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Other Organizations. Conference of Transportation Trades, Executive Board, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- International Affairs. General, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Contains correspondence in re Japanese Exchange Program
- International Affairs. Japanese Exchange Program, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- International Affairs. Japan Productivity Center Team, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- International Affairs. State Department Papers, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  State Department exchange programs with international railroaders.
- International Affairs. Agenda - Nashville Visit, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  For international railroaders visit.
- International Affairs. Office of International Labor Affairs, Bureau of International Labor Affairs (ILAB), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- International Affairs. International Labor Office (ILO), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13a)
- International Affairs. Office of International Labor Affairs, Team Managers, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13b)
- International Affairs. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  AFL-CIO withdraws.
- International Affairs. Press Release, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  On plane hijacking.
- International Affairs. Information Bulletin, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- International Affairs. International Transport Workers Federation (ITF), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Contains the Constitution of the International Transport Workers Federation (ITF).
- International Affairs. ITF Affiliation Fees, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- International Affairs. ITF Finances (Includes Special Report), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- International Affairs. RLEA, ITF Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- International Affairs. ITF Circulars, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- International Affairs. ITF Executive Board, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- International Affairs. ITF Management Committee, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Confidential report
- International Affairs. ITF Management Committee, September Meeting Agenda, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- International Affairs. ITF General Secretary, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- International Affairs. ITF Regional Activities, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  Buenos Aires. Spanish language newspaper clippings.
- International Affairs. ITF, Harold Lewis, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- International Affairs. ITF Regional Affairs, Africa - (Laflamme), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- International Affairs. ITF Regional Affairs, Africa - Senegal, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  Correspondence with M'Baye, Amadou.
- International Affairs. ITF Regional Affairs, Latin America, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  Contains map of railroads in Central America
- International Affairs. ITF Regional Affairs, Argentine Situation, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- International Affairs. ITF Regional Affairs, Asia (Iran), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  Map of Iranian railroad and informational packet.
- International Affairs. ITF Budget, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- International Affairs. ITF Railwaymen's Section, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- International Affairs. ITF Civil Aviation Section, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- International Affairs. ITF Seafarers' and Dockers' Section, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- International Affairs. ITF Fishermen's Section, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- International Affairs. ITF Asian Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Commuter Problems. General, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  Includes correspondence in re Inter City Rail Passenger Service costs
- Commuter Problems. Passenger Service Investigation, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  Includes recommendations to President Nixon, investigation reports, and correspondence.
- Commuter Problems. Investigation of Costs of Intercity Rail Passenger Service, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  Final report of ICC.
- Commuter Problems. Investigation of Costs of Intercity Rail Passengers Service, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  ICC report.
- Commuter Problems. Interstate Commerce Division Investigation, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Drafts of ICC report.
- Commuter Problems. Interstate Commerce Division Investigation, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Statistics for ICC report.
- Commuter Problems. Philadelphia Service Improvement Corporation, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Commuter Problems. New Haven Problem including New York Area (Long Island and Staten Island), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Includes information on MTA, Northeast Corridor and New Haven improvement plans.
- Commuter Problems. BART - Bay Area Rapid Transit, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Commuter Problems. Port Authority - Trans Hudson, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies - Passenger Service - Southern Pac between California and Louisiana, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Docket # 34733
- Commuter Problems. RLEA ICC Investigation, Suspense Docket 8436: Penn Central Elimination of Baggage Checking, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Case filings and correspondence. The ICC rejected this petition from Penn Central.
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Service Improvements - HUD - Mass Transit Grants, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Commuter Problems. Sec. 13(c) Agreement - Massachusetts Bay Transit Authority (MBTA), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Commuter Problems. Sec. 13(c) Agreement - Chicago Transit Authority (CTA), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Commuter Problems. Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Project, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Includes Agreements with SEPTA
- Government. National Mediation Board, Annual Report, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- RLEA. 1970 File Guide (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Government. Executive Branch, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Government. House and Senate, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Government. Congressional Campaign Contribution Requests, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Government. Government Agencies, General, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Government. Public Advisory Committees [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 14, Folder 20a)
  Membership directories
- Government. Public Advisory Committees [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 14, Folder 20b)
- Government. U.S. National Committee in Pan American Railway Congress, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Includes conference report in Spanish.
- Government. Treasury Department, General, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Government. Labor-Management Manpower Policy Committee, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Government. National Defense Executive Reserves, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Government. Department of Transportation, General, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Includes "Preliminary Report on Basic National Rail Passenger System."
- Government. National Transportation Safety Board (DOT), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Includes accident reports and annual report to Congress.
- Government. Staff Appointments (DOT), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Government. Transportation Association of America, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Includes NTSB safety studies and accident reports.
- Government. National Transportation Safety Board, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Government. Federal Railroad Administration (DOT), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Government. Staff Appointments (FRA) (DOT), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Government. Office of High Speed Ground Transportation, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Government. Railroad Safety Task Force, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Government. Bureau of Railroad Safety, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Includes accident reports
- Government. Safety - Rules, Regulations, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Includes pamphlet "Rules and Regulations for the Government of Railroad Safety and Sanitation" for West Virginia.
- Government. Safety Appliance Acts, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Government. Highway Grade Crossing Matters, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Government. Power Brakes, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards, and Instructions Cases in re Signal, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Government. Approval of Changes in Signal Installations, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Government. Hours Service of Service, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Government. Accident Reports and Governing Regulations, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Includes statistical data and annual reporting on accidents.
- Government. Labor Department - General, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Includes annual report for Department of Labor.
- Government. Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Standards, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission - General, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Government. ICC Membership and Staff Appointments, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Government. ICC Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure 106:2, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Government. ICC Statistics, M-300 Reports, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Government. Statistics 240 Motive Power and Car Equipment, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Government. Statistics 100-150 Operating Revenues and Expenses, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Government. Statistics 200 Operating Statistics of Large Steam Railways, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Government. Statistics 220 Revenue Traffic, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Government. Statistics 125 Selected Income and Balance Sheets, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Government. Statistics 300-350 Steam Railways. Class I Wages, Month, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Government. Statistics 210 Train and Yard Service, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission Car Service Orders, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Government. Motor Carriers - General, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Government. National Mediation Board - General, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  Includes reports on Emergency Boards 177 and 178
- Government. National Mediation Board. Public Law Decisions on Procedural Questions, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Government. National Mediation Board. Membership and Staff Appointments, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Government. National Mediation Board. Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Government. National Mediation Board. Amends re Individuals as Bargaining Agents, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Government. National Mediation Board. Decisions and Certifications, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - General, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - Third Division, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - First Division, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - Second Division, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - Fourth Division, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Orgs. Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Membership, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Application of Awards, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - Third Party Notices, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, General [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10a)
  Information on changes to tax law under President Nixon that affect the retirement plan dividends.
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board General [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10b)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, General, File #2 [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12a)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, General, File #2 [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12b)
  Includes bound volumes containing statistical analysis of finances.
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Reports for RLEA Meeting on [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13a)
  Includes pamphlet "Railroad Retirement Tax Tables."
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Reports for RLEA Meeting on [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13b)
  Includes envelope "What everyone need to know," with pamphlets on changes to Railroad Retirement for mailing to members.
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Administrative Practices and Procedures, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Status of Funds, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Retirement and Unemployment Insurance [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 17a)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Retirement and Unemployment Insurance [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 17b)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Educational Program, Meetings, Films, Etc., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Press Releases, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Supplemental Retirement Plans, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  Contains pamphlet "The 1970 Amendments to the Supplemental Annuity Program."
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers' Memoranda, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Government. Administration of Medicare - Financial Intermediary, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Government. Commission on Railroad Retirement, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  Thank you letters from every member of Congress from RLEA in re information packet on Railroad Retirement.
- Government. President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corp. [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 25a)
  Includes Report given to the Secretary of Transportation on the creation of a National Rail Passenger System.
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corp. [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 25b)
  Includes Report given by the Secretary of Transportation, John Volpe, on the creation of a National Rail Passenger System.
- Government. President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Government. Civil Rights (Agenda Item 2:19) (formerly 3.66), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Judicial. General, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Includes filings on a Claim resulting from the abandonment of the Memphis Terminal Station and Writs of Certiorari filed with the Supreme Court in re the abandonment of lines by the Santa Fe.
- Judicial. Jacksonville Terminal, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Includes Finding of Facts and Conclusion of Law in the civil rights suit against the carriers and the unions. Florida district court found in favor of the defendants. File contains notice from the DoJ that the government will attempt to appeal ruling to the Supreme Court.
- Judicial. Jacksonville Terminal, Legal Bills from Counsel, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- RLEA. General, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Includes December 1970 issue of "National Journal."
- RLEA. Constitution and By-Laws, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Includes amended By-Laws.
- RLEA. Officers and Members, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Letter from Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters in re whether the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers still has a "color clause" for determining membership eligibility.
- RLEA. American Railway Supervisors Associations, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- RLEA. American Train Dispatchers Association, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Information on attempt to pass a "Right-to-Work" law in Oregon.
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- RLEA. Brotherhood Railway Carmen of the U.S. and Canada, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- RLEA. International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- RLEA. National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- RLEA. Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- RLEA. Railway Employes' Department, AFL-CIO, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  Requesting affiliation with the RLEA
- RLEA. Canadian Affairs, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  Name changed to "Canadian Railway Labour Association." Includes By-Laws.
- RLEA. Miami Meeting of RLEA, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  Letters from various Florida hotels inviting RLEA to hold meeting at their facility.
- RLEA. RLEA Meetings - General, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  Planning documents for monthly meeting in various cities. Minutes of meetings.
- RLEA. Miami Meeting of RLEA, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Panning documents, brochures and correspondence.
- RLEA. Agendas of monthly meetings, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- RLEA. Reports of Counsel, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- RLEA. Assessments, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- RLEA. Wages and Rules General, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- RLEA. Radio-Telephone Equipment Communications, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway Strike, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  Remarks by Senator Wayne Morse, Oregon, on the Non-Operating Crafts Strike now entering its second year.
- RLEA. Compulsory Retirement, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- RLEA. 1968 Wage- Rules Movement, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- RLEA. 1969 Wage-Rules Movement, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- RLEA. Wage-Rules Movement, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- RLEA. Health and Welfare, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  Information in re Travelers' Insurance policies.
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Co., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  Group Policies
- RLEA. Railway Labor Building, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  Financial reports.
- RLEA. Washington Job Protection Agreement Cases (Files In WJPA Cabinet), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- RLEA. Committees - General, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- RLEA. Safety Committee, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- RLEA. Executive Committee, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- RLEA. Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, Etc., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- RLEA. Committee to Meet with AAR, Railroad Labor-Management Relations, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- RLEA. AAR-RLEA Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Newspaper articles on implementation of Civil Rights bills.
- RLEA. Political Education Committee (PEC), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- RLEA. Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- RLEA. In-Plant Education Program for Cooperating Railroads and Brotherhoods (Chicago Area), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- RLEA. Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- RLEA. Passes, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- RLEA. Personnel Records - General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- RLEA. Financial, General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Correspondence in re the division of finances between RLEA and the Congress of Railway Unions after six member unions left RLEA to form the new organization.
- RLEA. Financial Statements, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- RLEA. Internal Revenue Service Forms No. 990, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- RLEA. Postage Meter, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- RLEA. Office Equipment - General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- RLEA. Addressograph - Multigraph Corporation, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- RLEA. Lawyers Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 18, Folder 14a)
- RLEA. Lawyers Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 18, Folder 14b)
- RLEA. Lawyers Bills - Jacksonville, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- RLEA. Strikes General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway Strike, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Shop Crafts Dispute, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- RLEA. Sunny Point, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- RLEA. Air Pollution (New Jersey), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Railroads. Railroads, General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  Brief on what would happen should the Central of New Jersey shut down completely. Also contains newspaper clippings on various mergers.
- Railroads. Penn Central, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Clippings and correspondence in re the Penn Central Bankruptcy
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Railroads. ASTRO Report, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  America's Sound Transportation Review Organization
- Railroads. The American Railroad Industry: A Prospectus, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  Published by ASTRO.
- Railroads. Association of Western Railways, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Railroads. National Railway Labor Conference, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  Contains AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center course catalog.
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Civil Rights Department, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  Contains numerous pamphlets on Civil Rights initiatives, including two articles by Bayard Rustin and one by George Meany.
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, COPE, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO Legislative Action Bulletin, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 32)